Andrew H. Grant

9417 Deer Spring LN, Charlotte, NC 28210 andrewhansgrant@gmail.com (704) 806-0727

I am a Data Scientist with both Python programming and real-world business experience who graduated top of my Masters degree class. Skilled in data aggregation, data transformation (ETL), data analytics, predictive modeling, machine learning, and visualization.

Relevant Experience

Data Science Analyst and Programmer (September 2020 - December 2020)

BrightDime - Charlotte, NC

- Masters degree internship
- Consulted with Financial Services firm to develop BI dashboard using dash library.
- Data extraction and transformation using SQL and Python.

Partner Success Manager (January 2018 - August 2019)

Cisco Systems, Inc. - Charlotte, NC

- Supported some of Cisco's largest WebEx Partners in a Partner Success role, including collaborating with Cisco internal teams to resolve partners' operational issues, guiding and educating partners on new products and Cisco WebEx version releases, and working to improve operational processes between Cisco and Partners.
- Assisted partners by highlighting retention issues and opportunities for adoption.

Business Analyst – Partner Success Team (May 2016-January 2018)

Cisco Systems, Inc. - Raleigh, NC

- Provided escalated assistance to Cisco WebEx product partners to better support their customers.
- Audited WebEx sites and provided site releases for new Cisco WebEx sites.
- Provided WebEx usage and engagement reporting to partners.
- Performed requirement analysis and configuration changes to client WebEx sites.

Planning and Goaling Segment Analyst (March 2015-May 2016)

Cisco Systems, Inc. - Raleigh, NC

- Audited Canadian regional sales agent goal sheets.
- Performed final audit for entire Canadian regional segment goals.
- Managed the submissions and the budget for French translations of Sales agents' goal sheet legal documents.
- Resolved sales goal projection issues that arose within the Canadian customer segment.

Education

University of North Carolina at Charlotte - Charlotte NC (2019 - 2020)

Master of Science, Data Science and Business Analytics GPA: 4.0/4.0

North Carolina State University – Raleigh, NC (2010 - 2014)

Bachelor of Science, Statistics

Presented at 2014 North Carolina State University undergraduate research symposium.

Andrew H. Grant

9417 Deer Spring LN, Charlotte, NC 28210 andrewhansgrant@gmail.com (704) 806-0727

Skills

- Experience using Python for data transformation and analysis, data visualization, NLP analysis, and machine learning.
- Experience with R performing data transformation and analysis, data visualization, and modeling.
- Experience using SAS Enterprise Guide and SAS Enterprise Miner.
- Expertise with SQL queries using MySQL and PostgreSQL databases.
- Proficient using Microsoft Word, Excel, and PowerPoint.
- Experience with AWS primarily leveraging S3, SageMaker, and Athena.